That's nice.
いいですね
People who are hungry...
腹が空く人...
Will it come out?
出る?
sink...
シンク...
want
欲しい
...
nice to meet you.
初 めまして
What do you think?
どうですか?
Are you nervous?
緊張してますか?
I'm nervous.
緊張してます
I've been feeling really nervous ever since.
さっきからね、なんかすごい 緊張がつたまってくるというか
OK?
大丈夫 ですか?
it's okay.
大丈夫です
Also, when we met earlier, I thought it felt good.
あとさっき待ち合わせのときは 気持ちいいと思ったんですけど
He's really tall, isn't he?
め ちゃ背高いですよね
How many centimeters?
何センチですか?
It is 173 cm.
173センチあります
It's almost the same as me.
ほぼ僕と一緒ですね
So you wore slightly higher-priced shoes, right?
それでちょっと高めの靴 履いとったじゃないですか
Messed up, oh!
めちゃめちゃ、おお!
I thought that was wonderful.
と思って 素晴らしいですね
I have long legs.
足が長い
Don't tell me?
言われないですか?
However, it may be said a lot.
でも、結構 言われるかも
It's amazing.
素晴らしいですよ
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
is that so.
そうですか
I feel good and want to do my best.
いい感じの 気持ちと頑張ろうかなって
yes.
はい
I'm asking you guys a question: What was your first experience?
皆さんに 質問させてもらっているんですけど 初体験は いくつ
Is it?
ですか?
It's embarrassing.
恥 ずかしい
How old are you?
いくつですか?
About 16 years old.
16歳ぐらい
Maybe you just met the other person properly,
相手はちゃんと 会 った だけとか、
What do you think?
どうですか?
It was my boyfriend.
彼氏でした
Where is it?
場所は?
I don't remember.
覚えてない
Don't you remember?
覚えてないんですか?
I guess I should try chilling for the first time.
初 めてのチレンスべきというか
That's the content, but how do you feel after it's over?
内容ってあれですけど、終わった後の 気持ちとかどうですか?
feeling?
気持ち?
What is it?
なんだろう?
I wonder if it's like this, or if it hurts a lot,
こんなもんなのかなとか、 めっちゃ痛かったとか、
It's such an impressive feeling.
そういう印象的な気持ちって
Feeling impressive?
印象的な気持ち?
What is it?
なんだろう?
I don't remember.
覚えてない
Maybe I don't remember.
覚えてないかも
Surprisingly, the people who remember it remember it in great detail,
意外となんか、 覚えてる方すごい詳細に 覚えてるんですけど、
For those who don't remember, I don't remember.
覚えてない方ってね 覚えてないですよ、
There are some people who say that, and I think there is quite a difference in that respect.
っていう方もいてて、 結構その辺の 開きがあんなと思うんです
But that's the impression I get, and I don't remember it.
けど、 そんな印象で 覚えてないってことって
After that, various things happened, I think until today,
その後、いろいろね、 今日まであったと思うんですけど、
Hey, this is just for one person.
ちょっとこれは、 一人ちょっと、
I wonder if I did a header chick, or something like that.
ヘッダイチックやったんちゃうかな というようなプレイとか、
Is there a location or something?
場所とかなんかあったりします?
Maybe not.
ないかもしれない
Can you swallow the pain?
痛って呑まる?
Yeah, the pain sucks.
うん、痛って呑まる
Maybe he's serious.
真面目なのかもしれない
Well, on the other hand, I've never done this before, but
じゃあ逆にこう、 したことないけど、
I want to try something like this.
こんなことしてみたいな っていう、
I guess it's just out of curiosity.
なんか、 興味本位というか、 なんかありますね
Eh, I wonder what it is.
えー、なんだろう
difficult.
難しい
In the song, it's about outside, revenge, etc.
歌で言うと、 外とか、復讐とか っていうの、
I think it's heavy,
重いと思うんですけど、
Maybe I don't understand.
わか んないかも
I don't know.
わかんない
I think I'm a bit naughty myself.
自分自身で自分のことは、 ちょっとエッチだなって思いますよ
Well, I think it's a little, a little, pretty good,
まぁ、ちょっと、 ちょっと、 だいぶいいやと思うんですけど、
Who is your boyfriend now?
今は彼氏は?
I'm not there.
いないです
So, after all, there are lonely nights, right?
ということは、 や っぱ、寂しい夜もあるじゃないですか
What do you do in such a case?
そういう時は、どうするんですか?
What are you going to do?
どうするんですか?
picture?
え?
It's a little embarrassing.
ちょっと、 恥ずかしい
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
After all, we have to go down there.
そこを、やっぱ、 降り下げていかないと、
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
secret?
秘密?
That's what a secret means,
秘密っていうことは、 そういうことになって、
I get a little bit of it, but what do you think?
ちょっと捉えちゃうんですけど、 どうですか?
What do you think?
どうだろう?
Assuming that, then,
そういうことを、 仮定して、 その時は、
Will you use your own sword, or?
自分の剣を使うのか、 もしくは、
Do you use tools? Is that so?
道具を使うのか、 そうなんですか?
After all, two generations of a family live in a woman's home.
やっぱ、女性の家に 一家二代は、
Isn't that what it is?
あれがあるじゃないですか
Does it make you tremble?
なんか、震えるやつ?
Of course.
的な
What do you think?
どうなんですか?
In secret.
秘密で
It's a secret, and I have it.
秘密で、それは持ってますよ、 っていう裏返しだと
Well, that's what it is.
やっぱ、そういうことなんですね
difficult.
難しい
Let's leave it at that.
そこは、そういうことにしておきましょうか
yes.
はい
I was asked to listen to this, and I look forward to hearing from you today.
聞かせてもらったんですけど、 今日はよろしくお願いします
please.
お願いします
Isn't that often said?
よく言われないですか?
It is said.
言われます
That's a good thing.
いいことですね
For a while, I was having trouble sleeping due to my height,
ちょっと、後身長に 寝を囚われてて、
I didn't realize it, but there's quite a bit of overlap.
気づかなかったんですけど、 結構重ねがあります
How many cups is it?
何カップぐらいですか?
About F.
Fぐらい
wonderful.
素晴らしい
Put your hands behind your back for a moment.
ちょっと、後ろに手を回す
Behind?
後ろに?
It's amazing how thin it is. I'm watching it.
細いのがすごい 視聴してますね、
this is.
これは
I want to look back for a moment.
ちょっと、そのまま後ろに 見たい
Only the upper body, jerking to the right, including the waist,
上半身だけ、右にグッと 腰ごと、
At the back.
後ろに
That's nice.
いいですね
Please look over here for a moment.
ちょっと、こっちに見ていただいて
Everyone came to the side, what do you think?
皆さんが横に来ましたけど、 どうですか?
Do you feel like you have a lot of energy?
気も多いって感じですか?
I can't say it upfront.
前にして言えませんもんね
A little too much?
ちょっと、やりすぎ?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Excuse me for being so embarrassing.
恥ずかしいところ、失礼します
amazing!
すごい!
The volume is so thin.
ボリュームが こんな細いのね
How about this?
これはどうですか?
Does everyone say that often?
みんなよく言われますか?
Is that one piece?
それってワンピースですか?
No, this is divided into upper and lower parts.
いや、これ上下分かれてます
Then, can I have you take off your underwear first?
じゃあ先に 下を脱いでもらっていいですか?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Could you please take off that skirt for a moment?
ちょっと、そのスカートも 脱いでもらっていいですか?
Can I have you take off that top too?
その上も脱いでもらっていいですか?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
I'm going.
行 きます
It's pure white.
真っ白ですね
amazing.
すごい
It's amazing.
素晴らしいです
The pure white part.
真っ白の部分
What do you think?
どうですか?
You will be touched by Mr. Kimoroge.
気もろげさんに触られます
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
That's surprisingly bold.
意外と大胆ですね
What does that mean?
それはどういうことなんですか?
What do you mean?
どういうことだ?
I'm having a rough time with my uncle.
おじさんのサワサワしてますけど
What's going on, uncle?
どうなってますか、おじさんの?
hard.
硬い
How much?
どれくらいですか?
About 5 years.
5年くらい
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Shall I check?
確認してみます?
Can I have you pull down your pants?
ズボンを 下ろしてもらっていいですか?
Just like this until the bottom
このまま下までズボ
hmm.
ン
What about your uncle?
どう ですか、おじさんのやつは?
What's going on?
どうなってますか?
It's getting bigger.
大きくなっている
How does it feel?
触った感じは?
hard.
硬い
Does your hard penis pass?
硬いおちんちゃん、合格ですか?
Just move your pants.
そのままパンツもずらして
What do you think?
どうですか?
yes.
はい
What should I do with this?
これはどうするんですか?
What are you going to do?
どうするんですか?
What shall we do?
どうするんだろう?
Squeeze it with your mouth.
お口でペルペルとく
But what about the old man?
しかし、おじさんのやつは?
I don't feel like it.
感想気がしない
thoughts?
感想?
big.
大きい
Who are you comparing yourself to?
誰と比べているんですか?
I haven't compared it.
比べてない
copper
どう
Is it, uncle?
ですか、 おじさん?
I'm getting nervous.
緊張になっていますよ
It's better if your hair is wet, right?
髪の毛がくくんぬったほうがいいですよね?
I'll do it.
やりますね
Can I skip doing that?
そうするのを飛ばしてもらっていいですか?
I want to wear this one too.
ちょっとこっちも着たきゃ
I?
私?
It's too late now.
今さら
I have to take off my pants.
パンツを脱いなきゃ
That's nice.
いいですね
It's better when your hair is wet
髪の毛がくくんぬったほうが
That's good, right?
いい ですよね?
It's better if your hair is wet, right?
髪の毛がくくんぬったほうがいいですよね?
On my grandfather's skin.
お じさんの肌に
May I?
いいですか?
Yeah.
うん
Be kind.
優しくね
Will you notice?
気づけます?
Looks happy.
うれしそう
Do the members feel it?
メンバーが感じるんですか?
Yeah.
うん
Does he look happy?
うれしそうなのか
Oh, that's amazing.
ああ、すごい
I feel fine again.
また元気になってしまう
It's no good if Peach-kun touches it either.
ピーチくんも触ったらダメです
First, let it flow.
まず、流します
My uncle will do it for you.
おじさんがね、してあげる
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Uncle, I'll make you feel better.
おじさん、気持ちよくしてあげる
No, I already had a lot of it.
いや、もうさっきいっぱいしてもらいました
Can you do more?
もっとしてくれる?
Yeah.
うん
Is the time just now okay?
さっきの時間いいですか?
I was very surprised.
とてもびっくりしてね
I'll finish it and come out again.
仕上がって、また出ちゃうから
Is it okay?
いいの?
What do you think?
どうなの?
good?
いい?
That's nice.
いいな
Third.
3つ目
Scary, right?
怖いでしょ?
most
最
high.
高
Uncle, I've been attacked again.
お じさん、またやられちゃったんですけど
It didn't really come out, it was on the second floor.
すっごい出てませんでした、2階の
It was a lot on my body though.
いっぱい体にかかってたけど
Yeah.
うん
What was it like?
どんな感じだった?
What does it feel like?
どんな感じ?
I don't know.
わかんない
It was warm.
暖かかった
It was important.
大事だった
Also.
また
Shall I get a bath towel?
バスタオル取るか
Is it okay to have the M-shaped reform done there?
そこでM字改革してもらっていいですか?
Move your butt forward a little more.
もう少しお尻を前に
That's nice.
いいですね
I'm doing it to myself.
自分にやってるよ
Is that what you do with those fingers?
その指でもそうやってるんですか?
What happened?
どうなった?
difficult.
難しい
Open it properly.
ちゃんと開いて
He showed me a rocket with a spoon.
スプーンで ロケット見せてくれた
Uncles all over the country are watching it, what do you think?
全国おじさんが見てますけど、どう思いますか?
difficult.
難しい
But I want to be seen.
でも見られたいんですよ
Try it yourself.
自分で触ってやってみて
It feels good.
気持ちいいっしょ
When you come here, please touch me.
ここに来たら触ってもらって
Properly.
ちゃんと
want.
欲しい
I said it.
言ったもん
Singhu.
シンプー
I don't like it.
嫌だ
Singhu.
シンプー
want.
欲しい
Can I get your right arm like before?
右腕をさっきみたいにこっちもらえる?
It's good that you're holding onto me.
握ってくれてていいから
oh yeah.
そうそう
I think it's coming out.
出そうなんだけど
I'll put it out.
出すよ